<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>thoughts on Existential with Zayyan</title>
    <link>https://syedzayyan.com/tags/thoughts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in thoughts on Existential with Zayyan</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://syedzayyan.com/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://syedzayyan.com/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 18:06:01 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://syedzayyan.com/tags/thoughts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A day in London without the tube</title>
      <link>https://syedzayyan.com/posts/a-day-in-london-without-the-tube/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 18:06:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syedzayyan.com/posts/a-day-in-london-without-the-tube/</guid>
      <description>Our perception of time is strongly linked to our memories. The more I experience things, the more I feel I have grown as a person and spent more time on this planet. The London tube sort of takes away that experience of traveling on foot or on a bus and seeing the city. I feel this way partly because I use the same line everyday, and probably see the same people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The world ends?</title>
      <link>https://syedzayyan.com/posts/the-world-ends/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 23:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syedzayyan.com/posts/the-world-ends/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s just that I put this article elsewhere lol for consideration. Let&amp;rsquo;s see :)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love Fight Club</title>
      <link>https://syedzayyan.com/posts/love-fight-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 09:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syedzayyan.com/posts/love-fight-club/</guid>
      <description>🔴 SPOILER ALERT
Fight Club the movie and the book are one of my favourites of all time. I think the way you perceive the story changes with your age. I felt like writing an appreciation post about the movie this cloudy morning in the aftermath of Eunice. I don&amp;rsquo;t know what that says about me, but the movie does get misunderstood a lot, which I have noticed in various Reddit posts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting Out</title>
      <link>https://syedzayyan.com/posts/starting-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 18:06:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syedzayyan.com/posts/starting-out/</guid>
      <description>Starting out is always harder than you expect. To be fair, continuing to do something is equally harder. Take blogging for example. I have started a couple of times now thinking I would write something or the other but I never stick to it. However, I did make a differently designed blog in a different language each time. I did land a freelance gig that way, improving my personal portfolios.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
