<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>thoughts on Existential with Zayyan</title>
    <link>https://syedzayyan.com/tags/thoughts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in thoughts on Existential with Zayyan</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://syedzayyan.com/profile_pic.jpg</url>
      <link>https://syedzayyan.com/profile_pic.jpg</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 20:25:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://syedzayyan.com/tags/thoughts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Killing Even Season 4 is not all that bad</title>
      <link>https://syedzayyan.com/posts/killing-eve-season4-not-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 20:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syedzayyan.com/posts/killing-eve-season4-not-bad/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Killing Eve season 4 is on the floors and amidst all the reviews that are bewitching the show, I digress - well not completely but you get the gist. At the time of writing 4 episodes have come out and I have some opinions. I feel Season 4 should have been Season 3, Vilanelle should get killed, Kenny shouldn&amp;rsquo;t have died and the Helené-Eve dynamic that is going on actually makes sense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A day in London without the tube</title>
      <link>https://syedzayyan.com/posts/a-day-in-london-without-the-tube/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 18:06:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syedzayyan.com/posts/a-day-in-london-without-the-tube/</guid>
      <description>Our perception of time is strongly linked to our memories. The more I experience things, the more I feel I have grown as a person and spent more time on this planet. The London tube sort of takes away that experience of traveling on foot or on a bus and seeing the city. I feel this way partly because I use the same line everyday, and probably see the same people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The world ends?</title>
      <link>https://syedzayyan.com/posts/the-world-ends/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 23:00:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syedzayyan.com/posts/the-world-ends/</guid>
      <description>As I sit across my laptop screen, panicking and being anxious about the point of existence, there are people with their worlds toppling over. To be fair I am anxious as a knock-on effect. Now if we have learned anything from the 1940s, you don&amp;rsquo;t even need balls to deharmonise the world. One ball is just enough. But we are human beings and we do not learn from our blunders. We make them again and again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love Fight Club</title>
      <link>https://syedzayyan.com/posts/love-fight-club/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Feb 2022 09:25:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syedzayyan.com/posts/love-fight-club/</guid>
      <description>🔴 SPOILER ALERT
Fight Club the movie and the book are one of my favourites of all time. I think the way you perceive the story changes with your age. I felt like writing an appreciation post about the movie this cloudy morning in the aftermath of Eunice. I don&amp;rsquo;t know what that says about me, but the movie does get misunderstood a lot, which I have noticed in various Reddit posts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting Out</title>
      <link>https://syedzayyan.com/posts/starting-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 18:06:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syedzayyan.com/posts/starting-out/</guid>
      <description>Starting out is always harder than you expect. To be fair, continuing to do something is equally harder. Take blogging for example. I have started a couple of times now thinking I would write something or the other but I never stick to it. However, I did make a differently designed blog in a different language each time. I did land a freelance gig that way, improving my personal portfolios.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
